anorak.co.uk 2008-06-23

# Anorak News | Terms & Privacy

Here at Anorak, we take the privacy of our readers very seriously and operate by the following guidelines.

#####  Personal information

We will not sell or pass your e-mail address or other personal details to any third party without your prior consent. Any information you do give us may be used for the effective running of competitions or used on an aggregated basis to help us formulate a picture of our readership’s demographics without disclosing any individual’s personal information. If you provide us with your e-mail address, its privacy will be closely guarded.

#####  Traffic Data

Anorak, like almost every other website, uses cookies. Cookies are a standard Internet tool that send a small amount of information from our web server to your web browser, allowing our server to collect information back from the browser. Effectively, it allows us to identify you (or more accurately, your browser) when you visit Anorak.

#####  Contact Us

If you have any questions about this privacy policy, please [contact us](http://www.anorak.co.uk/write_to_editor.php) and we promise to get back to you with an answer as soon as possible.

February 2005

www.Anorak.co.uk

Anorak UK Ltd

+44 (0)7980 578831 (mobile)

___________________________________

**These terms and conditions** govern your use of this website. If you do use this website, you agree to be bound by these terms and conditions. If you don’t agree with them, please do not use the website.

This site is owned and operated by Anorak UK Ltd.

#####  Copyright

All copyright within the website is owned by Anorak UK Ltd and its licensors. All rights are reserved.

If you believe that any of the other pictures on site are under copyright, please contact us and we will remove them as soon as possible.

#####  Conditions of use

The contents of this website may not be copied, reproduced, distributed, republished, downloaded, displayed or transmitted in any form or by any means without the prior written permission of Anorak UK Ltd.

You may link to, but not replicate, the content on the website. You must not frame the site within any other website, borders or frames without the prior written permission of Anorak UK Ltd.

Anorak UK Ltd does not make any warranty or representation as to the accuracy or fitness for purpose of any material on this website or the reliability of the access to this website.

Anorak UK Ltd will not, in any event, accept liability for damages, loss or negligence resulting from use of this website. Anorak UK Ltd makes no warranty that this website is free from computer viruses.

This website contains advertisements, editorial and photographs submitted by third parties. Anorak UK Ltd excludes all liability for any illegality arising from, or error, omission or inaccuracy, in such material. This website also contains links to other websites that are not controlled by Anorak UK Ltd and which Anorak UK Ltd does not necessarily endorse.

#####  Discussion Forums

This site includes forums for discussion among users of this website. Anorak UK Ltd does not control contributions to the forums but reserves the right to delete, move or edit any contributions and to terminate your access to the forums.

In using the forums, you agree not to collect data on other users, or to publish messages that:

  * contain advertising or spam
  * promote goods and services
  * contain unlawful, threatening, abusive, intimidating, libellous, indecent or illegal content
  * Contain harmful viruses or code

You agree to indemnify and hold harmless e-go editorial services ltd from all claims, costs and expenses arising out of any messages posted or published by you. Anorak UK Ltd has no control over the accuracy or tone of messages posted by users, so you must bear all risk associated with your use of the forum.

#####  Anorak e-mails

Anorak UK Ltd allows you to subscribe to its daily e-mail containing updates of the website’s contents, subject to these same Terms and Conditions.

#####  Governance

Use of this website shall be subject to the laws of England.

Here at Anorak, we take the privacy of our readers very seriously and operate by the following guidelines.

#####  Personal information

We will not sell or pass your e-mail address or other personal details to any third party without your prior consent. Any information you do give us may be used for the effective running of competitions or used on an aggregated basis to help us formulate a picture of our readership’s demographics without disclosing any individual’s personal information. If you provide us with your e-mail address, its privacy will be closely guarded.

#####  Traffic Data

Anorak, like almost every other website, uses cookies. Cookies are a standard Internet tool that send a small amount of information from our web server to your web browser, allowing our server to collect information back from the browser. Effectively, it allows us to identify you (or more accurately, your browser) when you visit Anorak.

#####  Contact Us

If you have any questions about this privacy policy, please [contact us](http://www.anorak.co.uk/write_to_editor.php) and we promise to get back to you with an answer as soon as possible.

February 2007

www.Anorak.co.uk

Anorak UK Ltd

+44 (0)7980 578831 (mobile)
